weargustin.com 2014-07-02

# Redefining premium menswear | Gustin

  * Contact
  * Press
  * Privacy Policy
  * Referral Program Terms and Conditions

* * *

#### Contact

We're always here to help. Don't hesitate to reach out.

Email: [team@weargustin.com](mailto:team@weargustin.com)

* * *

* * *

#### Press

Please reach out to us directly with any press inquiries - [team@weargustin.com](mailto:team@weargustin.com)

Gustin has been covered by [Esquire](http://www.esquire.com/blogs/mens-fashion/gustin-jeans-010713), [Superfuture](http://superfuture.com/supernews/online-gustin), [Uncrate](http://www.uncrate.com/stuff/gustin-denim/), [Cool Material](http://coolmaterial.com/style/gustin-selvage-denim/), [Rawr Denim](http://www.rawrdenim.com/2013/01/gustin-hand-crafted-crowd-sourced-delivered-to-you-denim/), Werd, [Inside Hook](http://www.insidehook.com/nation/off-the-cuff/) and many others.

* * *

* * *

#### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Gustin collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.weargustin.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Gustin.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

Gustin may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service. Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize user experience. We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To improve our Site. We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * To process payments. We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature. To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails.We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

Marketing Opt-In and Opt-Out Provision

When you register, you will be given the option to opt-out of subscribing to our regular update service which will send you: Email alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about Gustin. We do not sell or otherwise pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes. Marketing communications you subscribe to will only be sent by Gustin. At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that particular mailshot. Simply follow the instructions in the e-mail.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Changes to this privacy policy

Gustin has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: Gustin www.weargustin.com 6 Mint Plaza, Unit 402, San Francisco, CA 94103 [team@weargustin.com](mailto:team@weargustin.com)

* * *

#### Referral Program Terms and Conditions

LIMITED TIME ONLY. 

To participate, refer friends who have not previously made a purchase from Gustin and are not current Gustin customers (each a “referred new customer”) by sending them the personal referral link provided to you as the recipient of this invite-only special offer. Each new customer you refer who clicks on your personal referral link will receive a store credit when they sign up for an account via your referral link and make a purchase of $80 or more prior to the referral offer's expiration or modification (a “qualifying purchase”).

During this limited time offer, each referring customer will receive store credit for each qualifying purchase made by a referred new customer. You may only refer up to one (1) member of your household to receive a promo code and a referral credit. The maximum referral credit any referring customer can acquire over the course of this limited time offer is $200.

In the event a referred new customer returns a purchased item and their lifetime order value decreases below $80, the referral credit awarded to the referring customer may be rescinded. Referring customers may not refer anyone who is an existing Gustin customer, including an existing customer with an account under an alternate email address. Referring customers may not use spam or send unsolicited emails to persons they don't personally know to collect referrals and may not collect referrals by posting on message boards. Gustin reserves the right to cancel a referring customer’s referral credit if it determines in its sole discretion that a referring customer has violated these terms, including through any fraudulent or misleading referral activity (for example, by referring fake people to Gustin, using false names, using multiple identities, email accounts or email addresses, impersonating another person, or otherwise providing false or misleading information) or if Gustin terminates the referring customer’s account for any reason. Referring customers may also be liable for civil and/or criminal penalties under applicable law. Any other abuse of this offer (including but not limited to hijinks and tomfoolery), as determined by Gustin in its sole discretion, may result in the rescission of the referring customer’s referral credit and cancellation of the referred customer’s discounted order, as well as a determination that one or both parties are ineligible to participate in this or future offers. Determination of referral eligibility and qualifying purchases, as well as any exceptions, are at the sole discretion of Gustin. Gustin reserves the right to verify and adjust credits at any time prior to or following posting and redemption.

Referral credit cannot be applied to previous purchases, and is not redeemable for cash. Offer not transferable. This referral program is subject to modification, suspension or termination at any time without notice in Gustin's sole discretion.
